

CONTACT

Mobile: +62 822 - 7295 - 8135

Email: fadhil.purnahar@gmail.com

Location: Tangerang, Banten.

Linkedin.com/in/fpurnahar

TOEFL ITP: 530

EDUCATION

INFORMATION TEGNOLOGY
POLITEKNIK NEGERI LHOKSEUMAWE |
2016 – 2020

SOCIAL MEDIA

Facebook.com/fadhilpurnahar

Twitter.com/fadhilpurnahar

Instagram.com/fpurnahar

Github.com/fpurnahar

Gitlab.com/fpurnahar

SKILLS

Swagger Open API Documentation

PHP, HTML, CSS, JS

REST API, JSON

Laravel Framework

Codeigniter Framework

DB SQL PhpMyadmin

UI / UX Designer

Bootrstrap, UI-Kit & Sass Style

Kafka

Docker Server

Redis Data By Memori

ElasticSearch Data By Memori

Arduino Programming

Linux System Operation

FADHIL PURNAHAR

BACKEND DEVELOPMENT

SUMMARY

Web Developer whit 3+ years of experience in designed and developing user interface, testing, debugging, and training within Website technologies. Proven ability in optimizing web functionalities that Improve data retrieval and workflow efficiencies. And Now I am focused on Backend Developer and Fast Learning to build a product that can provide value and impact for many people.

EXPERIENCE

BACKEND DEVELOPMENT

PT. BANK RAKYAT INDONESIA, Tbk | SUDIRMAN, JAKPUS | 08-2021 / Work

Revamp Swagger Open API Documentation (Laravel Lumen)

Revamp Database MySql.

Build Data Using Redis

Build Data Using ElasticSearch

Build End Run Docker on Development & Production.

BACKEND DEVELOPER

PT. YUKK KREASI INDO | TANGERANG, BANTEN | 04-2021 / 07-2021

Build CMS Accounting.

Build CMS Jurnal Accounting.

Build CMS YUKK2

Build CMS YUKK Merchant.

Build DataBase Migration.

FRONTEND DEVELOPMENT

PT. DEWABISNIZ DIGITAL INDO | BEKASI, JAKARTA | 01-2021 / 03-2021

Wordpress Development Template.

Build Laravel Template Web-Store

Build Addons WHMS.

Design Templates Website Using Modern Sass End Bootstrap.

PROGRAMMER

CV. MAKMU JAYA ALFA | LHOKSEUMAWE, ACEH | 2018 -2020

Programming microcontroller Arduino.

Electronic and electrical wiring diagrams Arduino microcontroller circuit and system analysis publishing for clients.

Design Templates Website Using Modern CSS Dan Bootstrap.

TEKNISI KOMPUTER

PT. SEJATI COMPUTINDO | LHOKSEUMAWE, ACEH | 2016 -2017

Maintenance Computer.

Maintenance Networking Computer.

Installation Hardware and Software

CERTIFICAT

- 2021 CODINGSTUDIO,ID / EXCELLENT TO MAKE A WEBSITE WITH LARAVEL.
- 2020 FULLSTACKDESINGNNER.ID / FULL STACK DESINGNER UI/UX.
- 2018 POLITEKNIK LINUX COMMUNITY / GENERAL SECRETARY.
- $\bullet \quad 2018 POLITEKNIK \, NEGERI \, LHOKSEUMAWE \, / \, FIELD \, PRACTICE.$
- 2017 POLITEKNIK NEGERI LHOKSEUMAWE / BASIC LEADERSHIP TRAINING.
- 2015 CISCO NET WORKING ACADEMY JP VEDC MALANG / IT ESSENTIALS.
- 2015 CISCO NET WORKING ACADEMY JP VEDC MALANG / CCNA ROUTING AND SWITCHING NETWORK.